I started looking at it very late
but no I am obsessed I had to try it I
shamefully bought this brand which is for me so this but
you Bill Shop's bags from box bags I really like
Masha's they had very
unique ones plus I got one
free so let's see how it is the packaging is
quite stable and cute no and this one
is also quite reusable first I
ordered the green one and the texture is the
answer you must be finding it very bright
but in personal it is a little scary the
second one is a perfect design such a texture
is very unique I did not see the story so I
think this is going to be my favourite and
with this the texture is maintained very well
and lastly I
bought the white one because it has two or three different
ethnic elements I thought that from Hero to
Fuel you in Batman the lowest one gets
free so density I want to
increase my order value plus shop I
like Indian numbers and winter I
love you back and on taste  But tell us in the comments which is
your favorite.